{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Asturias",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Cangas_de_On\u00eds",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Kingdom of Asturias is Cangas de On\u00eds.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9513872861862183,
            "question": "Which kingdom has Cangas de On\u00eds as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8871111273765564,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Kingdom of Asturias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5827317237854004,
            "question": "How does Cangas de On\u00eds contribute to the culture of Asturias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5747805237770081,
            "question": "Where is Cangas de On\u00eds located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5537122488021851,
            "question": "Is Cangas de On\u00eds a significant city in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4965413212776184,
            "question": "What are some notable events that have taken place in Cangas de On\u00eds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4825845956802368,
            "question": "What is the historical importance of Cangas de On\u00eds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4821677505970001,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Cangas de On\u00eds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42738792300224304,
            "question": "What is the population of Cangas de On\u00eds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33388710021972656,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions in Cangas de On\u00eds?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Kingdom of Asturias is Cangas de On\u00eds.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8862_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Cangas de On\u00eds?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8862_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous landmarks in Cangas de On\u00eds?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8862_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the historical importance of Cangas de On\u00eds?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8862_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8862_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to one of the provided documents, Cangas de On\u00eds was the capital of the Kingdom of Asturias until 774, but it does not specify that it remained the capital after that. In fact, another document states that the capital was moved to Oviedo in the 9th century. Therefore, at some point after 774, the capital of the Kingdom of Asturias is likely no longer Cangas de On\u00eds."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that \"Cangas de On\u00eds was the capital of the Kingdom of Asturias.\" Specifically, multiple documents indicate that Cangas de On\u00eds held this status until it was moved to Oviedo in the 9th century."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Cangas de On\u00eds was the capital of Kingdom of Asturias until 774, but then it was moved to Oviedo in the 9th century. Therefore, as of the 9th century, Cangas de On\u00eds is no longer the capital of Kingdom of Asturias.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}